MD AZAD

WORDPRESS WEBSITE DESIGNER AND DEVOLOPER





f Azad8433

in mdazad24

Bē mdazadhossen

About Me

"I am a Front-End Developer at FYA, dedicated to helping corporations and agencies create their desired websites. With my expertise in front-end development, I work closely with designers devoloper, and project managers to ensure that each website is not only visually appealing but also functional and user-friend-

Education

Chandpur Govt National University

Bachelor's Degree, Small Business Administration / Management

2020-2024

Machimpur Fazil Madrasah

Calss Xi and Xii in Management

2018-2019

Experience

WORDPRESS ELEMENTOR & WOO-COMMERCE EXPERT COALITION TECHNOLOGIES FEB 2020 - JULY

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER RE-GROUP MASS NOTIFICATION | AUG 2019 - JAN 2020

FRONT END ASSISTANT (INTERN) **STANDARD FORGE FEB 2019 -JULY 2019**



Contact

mdlazad0@gmail.com

Chandpur, Dhaka, Bangladesh

+880-1638512035

PORTFOLIO



https://bit.ly/3UKj4Di

Skills













Language

BANGLA

ENGLISH

HINDI